Sam Jann T

SKILLS

React · Vue · Angular · ASP.NET ·

Node.js · MongoDB · Javascript ·

Typescript · Laravel · PHP ·

Tailwind CSS · Next.js · Python · MySQL ·

PostgreSQL · C#

Full Stack Developer | React, Vue, Angular | Express, ASP.NET

Bogota, Colombia

SUMMARY

I am a Senior Full-Stack developer with over 8 years of experience. I have been working with IT for more than 12 years. I specialize in React, Vue, Angluar for Front-end and Express, ASP.NET for Back-end. I am going to work in upwork.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Developer

03/2022 - 06/2024

LARS Software Company

Bogota, Colombia

Configured Terraform from scratch for the monorepo project that serves several front ends at once.

- Planned and architected a process to convert several front ends into a single repository following monorepo standards with Nx and Next.js.
- Developed a conversion tool to migrate Contentful apps into KeystoneJS CMS.
- Designed and implemented a CI/CD pipeline to cover the monorepo approach, saving time not to redeploy non-affected projects.

Senior Full-stack Node.js Developer

05/2019 - 02/2022

DIGITAL WARE

Bogota, Colombia

Developed the back-end architecture from the top using Node.js as the main technology.

- Architected and implemented the application inside the AWS environment.
- Created a task scheduler that handles time-zones issues among global users to ensure that the clients receive their tasks at the correct time period.
- Integrated several social logins such as Facebook and Instagram.
- Integrated financial banking into the back end following security patterns.
- Maintained and created new features in their back end.
- Acted as a lead back-end software engineer and supported and maintained the AWS environment that held EKS, SES, and RDS, to name a few.
- Integrated external communication services such as SendGrid and Twilio.

Full-stack Engineer | Node.js/React Developer

01/2016 - 05/2019

Leanware

Bogota, Colombia

Developed an internal application from scratch using React, NestJS, and GraphQL.

- Integrated the offered design pages and made them responsive on mobile, tablet, and desktop.
- · Created the OAuth flow using AuthO as an external provider.
- Extracted huge data information stored in the client's AWS S3 bucket.
- Created a back-end server using NestJS and GraphQL with Relay.
- Used the company design framework made with styled-components and created custom styled-components to match with the project requirements.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer science

2013 - 2017

University of the Andes

Bogota, Colombia

LANGUAGES

English Proficient •••• Spanish Native ••••